# PEARL CHRISTIAN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER &

**FACILITATOR** 

### **CONTACT INFO**

- Nigeria
- +234 8152 583 776
- pearlchristian6@gmail.com
- pearly-c.github.io/portfolio
- linkedin.com/in/pearl-christian
- github.com/Pearly-c

### **EDUCATION**

2019-2019

NIIT

Benin City, Edo Sate

Diploma: Web Development

2012-2016

Ota, Ogun Sate

Bells University of Technology

Bachelor of Science: Industrial Chemistry

# SOFT SKILLS

Good communication problem-solving

Team-work

Creativity

Willingness to learn

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An ambitious, problem-solving front-end web developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Self-motivated, passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines.

Interested in a role with a well-established organization that appreciates dedication and hardwork. Available to work remotely.

# **WORK HISTORY**

### 08/2021 - CURRENT EMPOWER HER COMMUNITY

#### **ENGINEERING LEAD**

- Collaborate with team members to identify and fix technical problems.
- Delegate tasks/assignments to team members.
- Generate monthly status reports that clearly reflects all accomplishments in a given month.

02/2022 - 04/2022

### **IDEATHINKERS LIMITED**

#### FRONT-END ENGINEER

• Implement UI components for web applications using ReactJs.

01/2021 - 02/2022

### MIDTOWN TECH HUB

# FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

- Build reusable code for future use, while striking a balance between functional and aesthetic design.
- Ensure web design is optimized for smartphones.
- Ensure brand consistency is maintained throughout design, while optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Perform detailed code review to improve code quality.
- Participate in training beginners in front-end web development.

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

**ReactJS** 

**Javascript** 

Git version control/Github

Responsive web design

Web performance optimization

HTML/CSS/Bootstrap